SHIVAM GUPTA

52, Sundersi road Berchha , Shajapur (Madhya Pradesh) +91-9993330227

shivamgupta1430@gmail.com

Github: shivamgupta2017

Experienced Software Engineer who can bring a diverse skill set and creative drive to software application development. Proficient at designing and formulating test automation frameworks, writing code in various languages, and feature development and implementation. Specialize in thinking outside the box to find unique solutions to difficult engineering problems.

Skills

- C, C++, Java, python, php(framework), Javascript, mysql(phpmyadmin), jquery, ajax, Angularjs, algorithms.
- Linux, Github

Experience

June 2017 - PRESENT

Bitibe Technologies, Indore - Software Engineer

- Working as a full stack developer.
- Involvement in various aspect of web and mobile application development.

Dec 2016 - Jun 2017

My India Kart Pvt Ltd, Indore - Intern

• Responsible for development and maintenance of various android and hybrid application.

Education

June 2015 - May 2017

VIT University, Chennai - MCA

- Involved and participated various technical non-technical fest.
- Organised various kind of workshops that helped in knowledge based learning.

Can have a look over my project over on github: shivamgupta2017